westportgolfclub.ie 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy

You are here: [Home](http://www.westportgolfclub.ie/) / Privacy Policy

At Westport Golf Club we take your privacy very seriously. We will only use your personal information to administer your account and to provide products and services you have requested from us.

**What information do we collect about you?**

When you join or visit our Club we collect only the information required to fulfil the contractual obligations. We may also collect further information required through our website which will allow us to contact you regarding events, open competitions and special offers we may have at the Club, and we only share your information with internal and external data processors.

For security purposes CCTV is in operation on the premises.

**How the information about you will be used**

We use the information provided for the following purposes:

  * To operate the Club and provide golfers with booking, event management and other services they request.
  * For internal club record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * To send information or promotional emails that we deem of interest, with the option to opt out from receiving these types of communications at any time. We do not share your data with external marketing companies who would contact you in this way.
  * To post results from open competitions and events in the clubhouse, on the club’s website and social media accounts, as well as the local press.

When you join as a member, book a tee-time as a visitor, enter a competition or society event, we may share your information with external and internal data processors (tee time booking reservation service provider and membership administration system). You may have opted in for us to correspond with you regarding our activities including events and competitions by way of post, telephone, email and SMS.  If you have previously consented to this correspondence you can opt out at any time by writing to or emailing us at [info@westportgolfclub.com](mailto:info@westportgolfclub.com).  Your personal data is controlled internally by the Club’s Data Protection Officer who adheres to the Golf Club’s internal data protection policies and procedures and has been satisfied by the privacy policy of all external data processors.

Otherwise, Westport Golf Club will not share your personal information without consent except where the Club has a legal obligation to disclose the information to protect the Club’s legal rights or to prevent fraud or illegal activity.

** ** **Individual Rights**

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of this information please email us at [info@westportgolfclub.com](mailto:info@westportgolfclub.com),or write to the Data Controller at the Club. This will be provided in a portable, machine readable commonly used format. If you believe that any personal information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly amend or erase any information found to be incorrect. At the time of collecting data you have the right to object to the Club holding certain information about you.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links or leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

At the time of collecting data you have the right to object to the Club holding certain information about you.

**Changes to our privacy policy**

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and will place any updates on our website. Please check this page from time to time to ensure you are happy with any changes.

This privacy policy was last updated on **23 rdMay 2018**.

**How to contact us**

If you need any further information please email us on [info@westportgolfclub.com](mailto:info@westportgolfclub.com) or write to us at

** ** **Westport Golf Club, Carrowholly, Westport, Co Mayo, F28 VY07, Ireland.**
